

徐碩文

Hi, I'm a 2nd-year master student working on novel HCI research in Interaction Design and Development Lab at National Chiao Tung University, Taiwan led by Prof. Da-Yuan Huang. Before that, I received my bachelor's degree in Industrial Design. Our previous works include MASQUE - a skin-stretching Head-Mounted Display generates haptic feedback on human face, GAITERS - a skin-stretching device generates haptic feedback on lower limbs, and GLISSADE - a weight-shifting digital pen to facilitate input. These works have been or will be presented at top-tier conferences, including CHI and UIST.

Taipei, Taiwan

https://shuowenhsu.nctu.me

\(+886 981 796 926

WORK EXPERIENCE

06/2018 - 09/2018 應用劇本實驗室 UX 實習生

09/2016 - 02/2018 皇田工業 - 車用部品設計 助理工程師

07/2015 - 09/2015 水越設計 Agua Design 設計實習生

CONFERENCE TALK

[UIST'19] Conference Proceeding Talk Masque < VIDEO >

October 20-23,2019 New Orleans, LA, USA

LANGUAGES

國語 母語

英語 流利 (TOEIC 965, TOEFL 101)

法語 中等

SKILLS















EDUCATION

國立交通大學

應用藝術研究所 工業設計組 2018 - 2020 指導教授:黃大源

國立雲林科技大學

工業設計系 2012 - 2016

法國特魯瓦高等商學院 交換學生 2014 - 2015

台北市立松山高級中學 自然組 2009 - 2012

PUBLICATIONS

[CHI 2020 Paper] Chi Wang, Da-Yuan Huang, Shuo-wen Hsu, Cheng-Lung Lin, Yeu-Luen Chiu, Chu-En Hou, Bing-Yu Chen Gaiters: Exploring Skin Stretch Feedback on Legs for Enhancing Virtual Reality Experiences

[CHI 2020 Paper] Kai-Chieh Huang, Da-Yuan Huang, Chen-Kuo Sun, Ruei-Che Chang, **Shuo-wen Hsu**, Chih-Yun Yang, Bing-Yu Chen Glissade: Generating Balance Shifting Feedback to Facilitate **Auxiliary Digital Pen Input**



Ţ Best Paper Honorable Mention Award

[UIST 2019 Paper] Chi Wang, Da-Yuan Huang, Shuo-wen Hsu, Chu-En Hou, Yeu-Luen Chiu, Ruei-Che Chang, Jo-Yu Lo, Bing-Yu Chen Masque: Exploring Lateral Skin Stretch Feedback on the Face with Head-Mounted Displays

SCHOLARSHIPS & AWARDS

2019 中華民國科技部

研究生出席國際會議獎學金

2019 國立交通大學應用藝術研究所 書卷獎

2016 新一代金點新秀設計獎 最佳設計獎/廠商贊助獎入圍

2014 中華民國教育部 學海飛颺獎學金

2012 國立雲林科大 入學成績優異獎學金